250 Bryant St. Mountain View, CA 94041 U.S.A.

ChangSeok Oh

Profile: https://shivamidow.github.io E-mail: changseok@gnome.org Mobile: +1 (404) 740-7896

Open-source enthusiast and hacker specializing in web technology and Linux-based systems. A WebKit and GNOME project contributor. 8 years of industry and 6 years of academic experience. Looking for opportunities in the Web browser, Emerging Web Technologies, Browser Security, Web Security & Privacy, Kernel, and Computer Graphics.

Skills

WebKit, Blink/Chromium, GNOME, Linux, C/C++, Python, HTML/CSS/Javascript, Objective-C, Java, OpenGL/OpenGL ES, Clutter, Computer Graphics, GTK+, eBPF, BCC, Ethereum, Git, OBS, Clang, LLVM, GStreamer, Tizen, Linux Perf, Bluetooth LE, ReactJS, React Native, Embedded system, Puppeteer

Education

08/2017 - 12/2022 08/2017 - 12/2022 03/2000 - 06/2008 Ph.D. student (ABD) in Computer Science, Georgia Institute of Technology, U.S.A. Dual M.S. in Computer Science and Cybersecurity, Georgia Institute of Technology, U.S.A. Dual B.E. in Digital Media and Computer Engineering, Ajou University, South Korea

Professional Experience

01/2023 - present	Sr. Software Engineer at TikTok Inc. in Mountain View, CA
	Working on Web Platform
06/2019 - 12/2022	Intern at Igalia, S.L. in A Coruña, Spain (cert.)
	Bring ANGLE backend for WebGL to WebKitGTK
	 Zero copy texture sharing between Mesa and ANGLE via Linux DMA buffer
	Research Text-To-Speach technologies to employ for WebKitGTK
05/2020 - 08/2020	Intern at Samsung Research America in Mountain View, CA
05/2019 - 08/2019	Build a web app for health data analysis with ReactJS (frontend) and Node.js (backend)
	• Built an automated system verifying the UI of a watch app by using the Tizen automation framework
	 Profiled memory usage and revealed possible memory leak of a watch app by using Valgrind
	• Implemented file transfer via Bluetooth LE in a React Native watch application
08/2012 - 03/2016	Software engineer at Collabora Ltd. in Cambridge, UK
	Developed hardware-based compositing based on Clutter in WebKit
	• Resource-efficient web browser based on GNOME Epiphany for Raspberry Pi 2+
	 Customized WebKit features and API set for Smart TV Alliance SDK
07/2008 - 08/2012	Assistant Software engineer at Samsung Electronics in Suwon, South Korea
	• Developed an in-house web layout engine for Smart TVs, Printers in C++
	• Implemented WebGL and Accelerated Compositing in WebKit EFL by using OpenGL ES for Tizen
07/2007 - 06/2008	Intern at Samsung Software Membership in Suwon, South Korea
	• Developed a 3D racing game using DirectX on Windows (video)

Academic Experience

01/2023 - present	Instructional Associate at OMSCS, Georgia Tech
	CS 6262: Network Security
05/2021 - 08/2021	Research Intern at Tandon School of Engineering, New York University
	Research an online ad privacy issue with Prof. Damon McCoy
08/2019 - 05/2021	Teaching Assistant at School of Computer Science, Georgia Tech
, , , -,	• CS 6262: Network Security, Design and Implement the XSS task using node.js and Chrome Extension
	CS 6035: Intro to InfoSec
08/2017 - present	Research Assistant at School of Computer Science, Georgia Tech
	Study privacy leakage in online ads
	Redesign chromium to block user tracking by web browser fingerprints
	Debloat chrome browser with feature sunsetting on the fly by binary rewriting
	• Developed a defense system against micro DDoS by profiling resources with HPC (Intel PCM, MBM)
	• Implemented an idle profiler that diagnoses off-CPU time in the multi-threaded programs using HPC

Open Source Projects

poil source 110jects	
Committer at WebKit (patches)	
• Contribute several web features for WebKitGTK (e.g., Form Validation, Gamepad API with libmanette,	
AVIF support with dav1d, Web Speech Synthesis with Flite and GStreamer, etc.)	
• Implement OpenGL ES backend for Accelerated Compositing.	
 Developed memory pressure handler that copes with out-of-memory on top of Linux cgroup. 	
 Enhance WebGL support and Fix layout and rendering issues 	
• Fix CVE security bugs in WebKit (CVE-2020-10018, CVE-2020-11793)	
Member at GNOME Foundation (patches)	
Translate GNOME Web and its Help document in Korean	
Contributor at Chromium/Blink (patches)	
Implemented a CSS spec called font-size-adjust	
Fix layout and rendering issues in Blink	

Publications

ACSAC 2022
ACM CCS 2022
ACM CCS 2020
ACM CCS 2020
arXiv:2205.00056
DeView: Confining Progressive Web Applications by Debloating Web APIs (paper)
Cart-ology: Intercepting Targeted Advertising via Ad Network Identity Entanglement (paper)
Slimium: Debloating the Chromium Browser with Feature Subsetting (paper)
Mitigating Low-volume DoS Attacks with Data-driven Resource Accounting (paper)

Patents

US 20110296323 Web page management method and apparatus and storage medium thereof
US 20110289110 Method of re-searching webpage and apparatus and storage medium therefor
US 20110093606 Interface method and display device
US 20110090165 Interface method and display device

Talks

12/09/2022 ACSAC 2022 in Austin, TX, U.S.A. (slides)
11/09/2022 ACM CCS 2022 in Los Angeles, CA, U.S.A. (slides)
12/07/2014 Web Engines Hackfest 2014 in A Coruña, Spain (slides)
09/29/2014 DEVIEW 2014 in Seoul, South Korea (slides, video)
10/27/2013 DevOn 2013 in Seoul, South Korea (slides)

Service

10/2021 Mentoring student participants in the Open-source SW Developer Competition, South Korea (citation)

Last updated: 01/31/2023